Guide to the Isidore Sydney Falk Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- General Correspondence, 1923-1983; Series I; 11 linear feet (29 boxes)
  - Adelberg-Aiken (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Adelberg, Arnold J., 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Aetna Life Insurance Company, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Aiken, George D., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Altmeyer-Altmeyer (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Altmeyer, Arthur J. (*), 1950-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      See also: box 41, folder 182 See also: box 55, folder 433 See also: box 55, folder 436 See also: box 55, folder 442 See also: box 58, folder 483-882 See also: box 83, folder 903 See also: box 103, folder 1188 See also: box 144, folder 2082 See also: box 151, folder 2200
    - Altmeyer, Ethel (Mrs. Arthur J.), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Amatruda, Thomas T., 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Arbitration Association, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1933, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Association of Medical Clinics, 1958, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations (*), 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    See also: box 23, folder 488-489 See also: box 24, folder 498
  - American Hospital Association (*), 1943-1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    See also: box 13, folder 1933-1937 See also: box 15, folder 2282
  - American Hospital Association (*), 1968- 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
  - American Hospital Association (*), 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - The American Journal of Hygiene, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - American Medical Association (*), 1931-1933, 1948, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    See also: box 15, folder 280-916 See also: box 103, folder 1192 See also: box 111, folder 1323 See also: box 150, folder 2195 See also: box 152, folder 2216 See also: box 173, folder VI, Folders 2637-2712,
  - American Medical Association (*), 1966-1978 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - American University, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Dewey, 1956, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Anderson, Odin (*), 1954-1966 (Box 1, Folder 23-24)
  - Anderson, Odin (*), 1967-1977 (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
  - Andrews, Irene Osgood, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Appleton (D.) and Company, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Aronson, Jesse B., 1960, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration (*), 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Association of University Programs in Hospital Administration (*), 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 30-33)
  - Axelrod, Joseph, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Axelrod, Solomon J. (*), 1959-1963 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Axelrod, Solomon J. (*), 1964-1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Bac - Bi (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bl - Bor (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Bos - Bri (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Bro - Bru (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bu - By (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Badgley, Robin F. (*), 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Baehr, Frank H., 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Baehr, George, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    See also: box 144, folder 2093
  - Ball, Robert M. (*), 1962-1977 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    See also: box 67, folder 661-882 See also: box 144, folder 2084 See also: box 158, folder 2284
  - Bamberger, Lisbeth (*), 1958-1966 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Barr, David, 1960, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Battistella, Roger (*), 1963, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Baumgartner, Leona, 1962, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Becker, Harry (*), 1954, 1960-1965 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    See also: box 139, folder 1199
  - Becker, Harry (*), 1966-1975 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Bellin, Lowell, 1967-1971 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Beloff, Jerome, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Benfer, Richard, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Berger, Edward J. (*), 1958-1968 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Bernanke-Bernays (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Bernanke, David, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Bernays, Edward L., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Bierring, Walter L.
    See: box 41, folder 184
  - Bigge, George, 1959, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    See also: box 58, folder 483-660
  - Biographical Encyclopedia of the World, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Birk, Peter (*), 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    See also: box 129, folder 1804
  - Blue-Cross-Blue-Shield (*)
    See: box 17, folder 326 See: box 103, folder 1188-1409 See: box 179, folder 2821-2846
  - Bluestone, E. Michael (*), 1947-1978 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Boas, Ernst P., 1943 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Boerstler, Edward W., 1932-1951 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Boerstler, Richard W., 1953 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Bordley-Boyer (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Bordley, James III, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Bortz, Abe
      See: box 82, folder 901
    - Boudreau, Frank, 1957-1958, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Boyer, E.F. (Box 3, Folder 59)
      See: box 58, folder 483-660
  - Brand, Morris, 1955-1956, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    See also: box 103, folder 1196
  - Brandon, Kenneth F., 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Braverman, Jordan (*), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Braverman, Jordan (*), 1964, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 61-62)
  - Breslow, Lester (*), 1957-1969 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    See also: box 144, folder 2085
  - Breslow, Lester (*), 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Brewster, Agnes W. (*), 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    See also: box 22, folder 445 See also: box 67, folder 661-882 See also: box 104, folder 1207
  - Brewster, Agnes W. (*), 1963-1970 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Brewster, Kingman, Jr., 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Brindle, James(*), 1956-1964 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    See also: box 130, folder 1820 See also: box 142, folder 2063-2068
  - Brindle, James(*), 1965-1969 (Box 4, Folder 69-70)
  - Brindle, James(*), 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - British Columbia, Health Insurance Commissioners
    See: box 19, folder 394-396
  - Britton, Gertrude H. (*), 1929-1930 April (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Britton, Gertrude H. (*), 1930 May-Jun, 1930 August-Dec, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 73-75)
  - Britton, Gertrude H. (*), 1932 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Bronfenbrenner, J., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Brown, Douglas R., 1963, 1966-1970 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Brown, Howard J., 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Brown, J. Douglas, 1967, 1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Brown, Ray E., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Brown, Virginia, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Bruce, Charles O. (*), 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    See also: box 95, folder 1048 See also: box 101, folder 1128-1187 See also: box 103, folder 1196
  - Brumn, John M., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Bugbee, George(*), 1957-1967 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    See also: box 58, folder 483-660 See also: box 143, folder 2068
  - Bundesen, Herman N. (*), 1928-1947, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Burlingame, L. L., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Burney, Leroy E., 1972, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Burns, Eveline M. (*), 1965-1966, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Butler, Allan M., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    See also: box 63, folder 585
  - Butler-Butler (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Butler, Allan M. (*), 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Butter, Irene (*), 1966-1968 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Ca (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Ch - Cl (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Co (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Cr - Cu (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Califano, Joseph A., Jr., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Callender, Marie, 1965-1972 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Campbell, W. Glenn
    See: box 70, folder 734
  - Canada, Department of National Health and Welfare
    See: box 28, folder 595
  - Canadian Public Health Association, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Cannon, Joseph E., 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Caper, Philip, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Carpenters' Health and Welfare Fund of Philadelphia (*), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - Carter, Genevieve W., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Carter-Mondale Campaign
    See: box 144, folder 2087
  - Cashman, John W., 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Cavanaugh, James H.
    See: box 62 folder 558
  - Chase, Robert A., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Cherkasky, Martin (*), 1962-1969 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Chicago Heart Association
    See: box 32, folder 72
  - Chicago, University of
    See: box 16, folder 313 See: box 28, folder 609
  - Chick, Louis
    See: box 84, folder 917-1045
  - Christgau, V.
  - Ciocco, Antonio, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc. (*), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Citizens' Committee for Children of New York, Inc. (*), 1968, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 100-101)
  - Clague, Ewan (*), 1952-1968 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    See also: box 104 folder 1211
  - Clark, Dean A. (*), 1953-1954, 1963-1974 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    See also: box 160 folder 2331-2333
  - Clay, John L., 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Clayman, Jacob, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Clevenger, C. B., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 104)
  - Cohart, Edward M. (*), 1962-1972, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 105)
  - Cohen-Cohen (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Cohen, Morris N., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Cohen, Wilbur J. (*), 1953-1955 (Box 6, Folder 106)
      See also: box 20, folder 405 See also: box 58, folder 483-882 See also: box 130, folder 1837 See also: box 144, folder 2088 See also: box 151, folder 2200
  - Cohen, Wilbur J. (*), 1961-1968 March-Dec, 1969-1974 (Box 6, Folder 107-112)
  - Cohen, Wilbur J. (*), 1975, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Cole, Jack W., 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 113)
  - Coleman-Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Coleman, Jules V. (*), 1963-1972 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Colman, Douglas, 1959-1960, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 114)
  - Commonwealth Fund (*), 1932-1933, 1936, 1968, 1970 January-December (Box 6, Folder 115-116)
  - Connecticut, State Department of Health, 1933 (Box 6, Folder 117)
  - Continental Casualty Company, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Cooper, Barbara
    See: box 27, folder 562-563
  - Cooperative Health Federation of America, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 118)
  - Corning, Peter A., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 119)
  - Corning, Peter A., 1966-1976 (Box 7, Folder 120-121)
  - Cotter, William R., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Crane, Robert T., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Crosby, Edwin L., 1953-1957, 1966-1972 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Crozier, Dan, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 123)
  - Cruikshank, Nelson H., 1955-1961, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 123)
    See also: box 25, folder 533 See also: box 125, folder 1681,
  - Cumming, Hugh S.
    See: box 3, folder 38
  - Cushing, Harvey
    See: box 13 folder 234
  - Da - De (Box 7, Folder 124)
  - Di - Dv (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - Daily, Edwin F. (*), 1953-1964 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    See also: box 105, folder 1232
  - Daily, Edwin F. (*), 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Daitz, Bernard D., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Dalton, Charles F., 1930 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Darley, Ward (*), 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Davis, Alice (Mrs. Michael M.), 1971, undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Davis (Leonard) Institute of Health Economics, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    See also: box 9, folder 163
  - Davis, Michael M. (*), 1920, 1928, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 129)
    See also: box 8, folder 143 See also: box 20, folder 413-415 See also: box 26, folder 547 See also: box 31, folder 46 See also: box 41, folder 190-193 See also: box 54 folder 424 See also: box 58-67, folder 483-660 See also: box 108, folder 1283 See also: box 156, folder 2250-2256 See also: box 157, folder 2266-2280 See also: box 160, folder 2331-2333
  - Davis, Michael M. (*), 1934 March-December, 1935 January-May, 1935 July- December (Box 8, Folder 130-133)
  - Davis, Michael M., 1936 January-June (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - Davis, Michael M. (*), 1936 July-Dec, 1937, 1944-1949, 1953-1956, 1959-1972, undated (Box 8, Folder 135-143)
  - Davis (Michael M.) memorial volume, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 144)
  - Dearing, Warren Palmer, Circa 1960-1961 (Box 8, Folder 145)
    See also: box 101, folder 1135 See also: box 119, folder 1498 See also: box 130, folder 1815 See also: box 160, folder 2318-2327
  - Dedmon, Robert E., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 145)
  - Denenberg, Herbert Sidney, 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 146-147)
  - Densen, Paul M. (*), 1959-1968 (Box 8, Folder 148)
  - Densen, Paul M., 1970, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 149-150)
  - Dentists' Supply Company, 1961-1962 (Box 8, Folder 151)
  - Dingell, John D., 1958-1962, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Dirlam, Joel B., 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 152)
  - Dirlam, Joel B. (*), 1972-1974 (Box 8, Folder 153)
  - Donabedian, Avedis (*), 1963-1968 (Box 8, Folder 154)
  - Dorn, Harold F.
    See: box 22, folder 460
  - Douglas, Paul H., 1933, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 155)
  - Dublin, Louis I. (*), 1903-1936 (Box 9, Folder 156)
    See also: box 3, folder 36
  - Dublin, Louis I. (*), 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Duff, Raymond S., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 157)
  - Duffy, Benedict J., 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Duffy, Joseph, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Dulles, Eleanor L.
    See: box 67, folder 661-882
  - Dumpson, James R., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 158)
  - Ed - Em (Box 9, Folder 159)
  - En - Ew (Box 9, Folder 160)
  - Eanam, W. Van
  - Ebbert, Arthur, Jr., 1963 (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Ebert, Robert H. (*), 1965-1972 (Box 9, Folder 161)
  - Edsall, Geoffrey, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 162)
  - Eilers, Robert D. (*), 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Einhorn, Daniel, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 163)
  - Eliot, Martha M. (*), 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Eliot, Thomas, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 164)
  - Ellickson, Katherine, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 165)
    See also: box 159, folder 2298
  - Elling, Ray H. (*), 1963-1971 (Box 9, Folder 165)
  - Elnicki, Richard A., 1968, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 166-167)
  - Emerson, Haven, 1930-1933 (Box 9, Folder 168)
    See also: box 3, folder 44
  - English, Joseph T., 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 168)
  - Enochs, Elizabeth Shirley, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Epstein, Abraham, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Epstein, L. E.
  - Epstein, Ronald B., 1967-1974 (Box 9, Folder 169)
  - Esselstyn, Caldwell B. (*), 1954-1960 (Box 10, Folder 170)
    See also: box 18, folder 346 See also: box 104, folder 1219 See also: box 160, folder 2319
  - Esselstyn, Caldwell B. (*), 1961-1968, 1975, undated (Box 10, Folder 171-172)
  - Esselstyn, (Caldwell B.) Foundation(*), 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 173)
  - Essl, Howard C., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 174)
  - Evang, Karl, 1958, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 174)
  - Ewing, Oscar R., 1953-1954 (Box 10, Folder 174)
    See also: box 67, folder 661-882
  - Excerpta Medica, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 175)
  - Fa - Fl (Box 10, Folder 176)
  - Fo - Fr (Box 10, Folder 177)
  - Falk, Leslie A.(*), 1958-1965 (Box 11, Folder 178)
    See also: box 107, folder 1272
  - Falk, Leslie A. (*), 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 179)
  - Farnsworth, Dana L. (*), 1961 (Box 11, Folder 180)
  - Farrisey, Claire G., 1962-1967, undated (Box 11, Folder 181)
  - Federman, David
    See: box 21, folder 430-477
  - Fein, Rashi, 1967-1973, 1981, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 181)
    See also: box 144, folder 2080-2249
  - Feldman, Jacob J. (*), 1963-1964 (Box 11, Folder 182)
  - Feldman, Louis L., 1969-1971 (Box 11, Folder 183-184)
  - Feldstein, Martin S., 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Felix, Robert H., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 185)
  - Fernow, L. Carol (*), 1967-1973 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Fetter, Robert B., 1964, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Fifer, A. W.
    See: box 69, folder 706
  - Filerman, Gary L., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 186)
  - Fine, Max W.
    See: box 144, folder 2080-2249
  - Finison, Lorenz J., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Fink, Raymond, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 187)
  - Fischelis, Robert P., 1960, 1969-1972 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - Fisher, Jacob, 1956-1958 (Box 11, Folder 188)
    See also: box 17, folder 326-349 See also: box 67, folder 661-882
  - Flash, William S., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 189)
  - Flexner, Abraham, 1932 (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - Flexner, Simon, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 190)
  - Folks, Homer, 1928, 1936-1937 (Box 11, Folder 191)
  - Follansbee, George E.
    See: box 3, folder 39
  - Follman, Joseph F., Jr., 1958-1962 (Box 11, Folder 192)
  - Follman, Joseph F., Jr. (*), 1963-1969 (Box 11, Folder 193)
  - Foote, Franklin M.(*), 1962-1973 (Box 11, Folder 194)
    See also: box 131, folder 1863
  - Forbes, William H., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Ford Foundation(*), 1965, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Ford, William, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 195)
    See also: box 104, folder 1202
  - Fortune, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 195)
  - Frank, Beryl, 1957-1958, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 196)
    See also: box 21, folder 431 See also: box 21, folder 433 See also: box 95, folder 1049
  - Frankel, John M., 1963-1971 (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Frankel, Peg (Mrs. John M.), 1962 (Box 11, Folder 196)
  - Frankl, George, 1943 (Box 11, Folder 197)
  - Frechette, Alfred L., 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - French, David M., 1970-1972 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Friedman, Maurice
    See: box 17, folder 326-373
  - Frost, Wade H., 1932 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Frothingham, C.
    See: box 63, folder 585
  - Fry, John, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 198)
  - Fuchs, Victor R., 1965-1974, undated (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - Fulton, Richard, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - Furman, Bess, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 199)
  - Furstenberg, Frank F., 1949, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 199)
    See also: box 159, folder 2296
  - Ga - Ge (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gl - Go (Box 11, Folder 201)
  - Goo - Gra (Box 11, Folder 202)
  - Gre (Box 11, Folder 203)
  - Gri - Gy (Box 11, Folder 204)
  - Gabrielson, Ira W., 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 205)
  - Gafefer, William M.
  - Galbraith, Douglas J.
    See: box 22, folder 445 See: box 22, folder 447 See: box 22, folder 449 See: box 22, folder 452
  - Gardner, John W., 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 205)
  - Garfield, James G.
    See: box 96, folder 1060
  - Garfield, Sidney, 1957, 1969-1977 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Gebhard, Bruno (*), 1961-1967, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 206)
  - Geerlings, Gerald K., 1942-1943 (Box 12, Folder 207)
  - Gegan, V. F.
    See: box 70, folder 731
  - Geibel, Edgar L., 1965-1970 (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - General Electric, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - Geomet, Inc., 1969, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 208)
  - George, Walter F., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Gerard, Ralph Waldo, 1931 (Box 12, Folder 209)
  - Gerig, Daniel S., 1947, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 209)
    See also: box 20, folder 402-404 See also: box 58, folder 483-660 See also: box 68, folder 681-882
  - Gerstley, Jesse R., 1930 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Giaimo, Robert N., 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Gillespie, John F., 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 210)
  - Gilmartin, William M.
    See: box 84, folder 926
  - Glaser, Robert J., 1964,1969 (Box 12, Folder 211)
  - Glasser, Melvin A. (*), 1964-1966 (Box 12, Folder 211)
    See also: box 26, folder 547-550 See also: box 13, folder 1817 See also: box 144, folder 2094
  - Glasser, Melvin A. (*), 1967-1969, 1972-1977 (Box 12, Folder 212-213)
  - Gold, Milton(*), 1959-1966 (Box 12, Folder 214)
  - Goldberg, Theodore I. (Ted) (*), 1963-1965 (Box 12, Folder 215)
    See also: box 107, folder 1281-1292 See also: box 113, folder 1364 See also: box 115, folder 1383
  - Goldberg, Theodore I. (Ted), 1966-1969 (Box 12, Folder 216)
  - Goldmann, Franz, 1937-1938 (Box 12, Folder 217)
    See also: box 74, folder 791 See also: box 119, folder 1471
  - Goldmann, Franz (*), 1943-1949, 1955-1969 (Box 12, Folder 218-219)
  - Goldmann, Franz, 1970, undated (Box 12, Folder 220)
  - Goldstein, George S., 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 221)
  - Goodenough, Ben, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 222)
  - Goodman, Leo
    See: box 25, folder 533
  - Goodrich, Annie W., 1923 (Box 13, Folder 222)
  - Gorman, Mike, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Gornick, Marian, 1976-1977 (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Grace, Edwin J. (*), 1950-1961 (Box 13, Folder 224)
  - Grant, John B. (*), 1953-1959 (Box 13, Folder 225)
  - Grasso, Ella T., 1969 (Box 13, Folder 225)
  - Greeley, David Mcl., 1962-1964 (Box 13, Folder 226)
  - Greenberg, Bernard, 1958-1965 (Box 13, Folder 227)
    See also: box 105, folder 1226 See also: box 111, folder 1333
  - Greenburg, Leonard (*), 1933-1959, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 227)
    See also: box 22, folder 445
  - Gregg, Alan
    See: box 143, folder 2077
  - Griffith, John R., 1963-1970 (Box 13, Folder 228)
  - Griswold, Don M., 1930 (Box 13, Folder 228)
  - Group Health Association (Washington, D.C.) (*), 1937-1953 (Box 13, Folder 229)
  - Group Health Association (Washington, D. C.), 1961-1971 (Box 13, Folder 230)
  - Group Health Cooperative of Puget Sound, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 231)
  - Group Health Insurance, Inc. (New York City) (*), 1960-1963 May-Jul, 1963 October-December (Box 13, Folder 232-233)
  - Gruenberg, Benjamin C., 1940-1945, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 234)
  - Gruenberg, Ernest M.
    See: box 95, folder 1052
  - Ha (Box 14, Folder 235)
  - He - Hi (Box 14, Folder 236)
  - Ho (Box 14, Folder 237)
  - Hu - Hy (Box 14, Folder 238)
  - Haber, William, 1940, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 239)
  - Haggerty, Robert J., 1968, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 239)
  - Haight, Eric H., 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 239)
  - Hamilton, Walton H., 1937 (Box 14, Folder 240)
  - Hamlin, Robert H. (*), 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 240)
  - Hansen, Horace, 1959, 1967-1972 (Box 14, Folder 240)
  - Hardy, James D. (*), 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 241)
  - Harper's Magazine, 1939, 1948, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 241)
  - Harris, Benedict R. (*), 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 241)
  - Harris, Oren, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 242)
  - Harris, Seymour E. (*), 1950-1956 (Box 14, Folder 242)
    See also: box 70, folder 734
  - Harris, Seymour E. (*) (Box 14, Folder 243)
  - Harris, Seymour E. (*), 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 244)
  - Harvard Community Health Plan (*), 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 245)
  - Harvard Law Review, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 245)
  - Harvard Medical School, Family Health Care Program, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 246)
  - Harvard University, University Health Services
    See: box 41, folder 180
  - Hatcher, Gordon H., 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 246)
  - Hathaway, John S. (*), 1960-1962 (Box 14, Folder 247)
  - Health Administration Press, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 248)
  - Health Information Foundation
    See: box 30, folder 23-26
  - Health Insurance Foundation
    See: box 34, folder 81 See: box 11, folder 192-193
  - Health Insurance Institute (*), 1958-1973 (Box 14, Folder 248)
  - Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York (*), 1958-1964, undated (Box 14, Folder 249)
    See also: box 3, folder 43 See also: box 32, folder 68-71 See also: box 7, folder 126-127 See also: box 41, folder 187 See also: box 14, folder 249 See also: box 24, folder 493
  - Health Professionals for Political Action
    See: box 18, folder 344
  - Health Research Council, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 250)
  - Hesse, Frank E., 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 251)
  - Hewitt, William F. (*), 1930-1939 (Box 14, Folder 252)
  - Hill Health Center (New Haven) (*), 1967-1971 (Box 14, Folder 252)
  - Hill, Lister, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 252)
  - Hilling, Helen C., 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 253)
  - Hirch, Nathaniel, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 254)
  - Hirshfield, Daniel S., 1965, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 254)
  - Hiscock, Ira V. (*), 1931-1953 (Box 14, Folder 255)
    See also: box 126, folder 1747
  - Hiscock, Ira V. (*), 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 256)
  - Hitchens, A. Parker, 1929-1930 (Box 14, Folder 256)
  - Hogness, John R., 1974 (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - Hopkins, Harry L., 1938 (Box 14, Folder 257)
    See also: box 41, folder 202
  - Horwitz, Abraham, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 257)
  - Horwood, Murray P., 1956 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - Hospital Service Plan of New Jersey (*), 1964-1966 (Box 14, Folder 258)
  - Hughes, John B., 1943 (Box 15, Folder 259)
  - Hull, Cordell, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 259)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (*), 1953-1972 (Box 15, Folder 260)
    See also: box 159, folder 2296 See also: box 159, folder 2300